Guide to the Ernst Weber Collection RG.033
Poly Archives at the Bern Dibner Library of Science and Technology, NYU Libraries
Ernst Weber Collection
1922-2002
1930-1992
Poly Archives at the Bern Dibner Library of Science and Technology, NYU Libraries
Weber, Ernst
RG.033
35
56 Cubic Feet 32 boxes
Ernst Weber was an award-winning and accomplished electrical engineer, pioneering advancements in the field both through his own research and his work in founding and running prominent institutions. He was a pioneer in the field of microwave technology. Ernst Weber was president of the Polytechnic Institute of Brooklyn (Poly) from 1957-1969. During his tenure Poly saw some of its greatest students and achievements, while Weber held together an institution struggling with financial distress and impending mergers. The papers of Ernst Weber include writings, awards, collected publications, a variety of items related to the university, papers of the Microwave Research Institute (now Weber Research Institute) and documents related to professional institutions.
Biographical / Historical
Weber was born in Vienna, Austria, on September 6, 1901. He was oldest of five siblings and the son of a homemaker and a railway worker. In 1924, Weber received a degree in Engineering from the Technical University in Austria. Immediately after he began working as a research engineer for the Austrian Siemens-Schuckert Company. Weber attended both the Technical University of Vienna and the University of Vienna concurrently. He studied philosophy, physics, and mathematics, earning his PhD from the University of Vienna in 1926. In 1927, he received his Doctor of Science from the Technical University. His studies of philosophy and engineering remained ingrained in his future work.
Weber's work with the Siemens-Schuckert Company allowed him to move to Berlin. There he taught at the Technical University of Berlin. In 1930, Weber was invited to teach as a visiting lecturer Polytechnic Institute of Brooklyn (Poly). The rise of Nazism in Europe influenced his decision to accept the position and to relocate to the United States. Weber became a permanent member of the Poly faculty the following year. In 1945, he helped found the Microwave Research Institute (MRI), which would later be renamed as the Weber Research Institute in his honor. This same year he was appointed head of the department of electrical engineering. He was inaugurated as the sixth president of Polytechnic in December of 1957.
A large part of Weber's work and focus while he was president was making the institution financially sustainable. This included many hours devoted to research, as well as tremendous outreach to donors and government officials in both New York City and State. A large portion of his exploration into sustainability focused on mergers with both New York University and the State University of New York. Poly shined during Weber's reign. He was able to apply his interests in philosophy, pedagogy, and engineering to lead the university towards sustainability in the face of financial crisis.
In 1958, he was elected president of the Institute of Radio Engineers (IRE). After the merging of the American Institute of Electrical Engineers (AIEE) and the IRE in 1963, Weber became the first president of the combined entity, the Institute of Electrical and Electronics Engineers (IEEE). In 1964, he helped found the National Academy of Engineers (NAE).
Weber would go on to hold over 50 patents in the field of microwave technology. He was a prolific writer covering fields from electrical engineering, to philosophy, often finding a meeting ground between them in his writings. Following his retirement from Poly, he moved to Columbus, North Carolina, where he passed away on February 16, 1996. He departed in the wake of his insurmountable legacy.
SOURCES Ernst Weber, an oral history conducted in 1991 by Frederik Nebeker, IEEE History Center, Hoboken, NJ, USA.
Scope and Contents
This collection contains the papers and writings of Ernst Weber, the sixth president of the Polytechnic Institute of Brooklyn. Many of the items in this collection regard his tenure at Poly, potential university mergers, writings, and a collection of volumes and clippings from relevant publications. There are also many items related to various professional affiliations, namely the Institution of Electrical and Electronics Engineers (IEEE), the National Academy of Engineers (NAE), and the Microwave Research Institute (MRI), now Weber Research Institute. The items in this collection represent a dynamic range, the bulk related to Weber's time at Poly, both before and during his presidency, as well as some items after departure.
When folders were found to have original titles or labels those titles were kept and noted by placing them in quotation marks.
Arrangement
The collection is arranged into seven series, by subject:
Series I: Biographical
Series II: Writings
Series III: Polytechnic Institute of Brooklyn
Series IV: Mergers
Series V: Publications
Series VI: Professional Organizations
Series VII: Oversize
Sponsor Note
This project was made possible in part by a generous grant from the History Programs, American Institute of Physics.
Conditions Governing Access
Open for research without restrictions.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Materials found in collection; there is no documentation concerning the provenance of these materials.
Brooklyn (New York, N.Y.); Clippings; Electrical engineering; Engineering; Reprints; Administrative records; Course materials; Monographs; Photographs; American Institute of Electrical Engineers; Institute of Radio Engineers; Institute of Electrical and Electronics Engineers; Polytechnic Institute of Brooklyn. Microwave Research Institute; Polytechnic Institute of Brooklyn; United States. Office of Naval Research; National Research Council (U.S.); National Academy of Engineering; National Academy of Sciences (U.S.)
- Series I: Biographical, 13245
  - Subseries A: Biographical and Personal, 14060
    - Biographical sketches, 1958-1993; 13912 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - "Autobiography 'Listen'", 1981-1984; 13913 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Ernst Weber Oral History, 1991; 13914 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - National Medal of Science, 1986; 13915 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Weber Scholarship, 1990; 13916 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Ernst Weber obituaries, 1996; 13917 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Ernst Weber personal correspondence, 1957-1976; 13918 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Weber headshots, undated; 13919 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Personal photographs, undated; 13920 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Greece trip photographs, 1977; 13921 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - "Greece Aegean Adventure", 1977; 13922 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - Maps and brochures, 1977; 13923 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - Travel clippings, 1980-1986; 13924 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Subseries B: Awards, 14061
    - Honorary degree citation, Newark College of Engineering, 1959; 13925 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - Honorary degree citation, Long Island University, 1963; 13926 (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - Awards and certificates on paper, 1969-1992; 13927 (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - Awards and recognition ceremonies, 1966-1990; 13928 (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - Ernst Weber Fellow of ABET certificate, 1988; 13929 (Box 1, Item 1)
    - Dr. Sonya Weber YWCA of the City of New York Award for Distinguished Voluntary Service, 1979; 13930 (Box 1, Item 2)
    - The George Washington University to Dr. Ernst Weber in recognition of valuable service to the School of Engineering and Applied Science plaque, 1971; 13931 (Box 1, Item 3)
    - Ernst Weber American Academy of Arts and Sciences Fellow framed certificate, 1966; 13932 (Box 1, Item 4)
    - Congressional Record honoring Dr. Ernst Weber mounted to plaque, 1986; 13933 (Box 1, Item 5)
    - Ernst Weber Army Scientific Advisory Panel plaque, 1958; 13934 (Box 2, Item 1)
    - Dr. Ernst Weber Electronics Advisory Group of the US Army Electronics Command plaque, 1971; 13935 (Box 2, Item 2)
    - Dr. Ernst Weber founding of PRD plaque, 1974; 13936 (Box 2, Item 3)
    - Separated piece from IEEE Education Society plaque, 1990; 13937 (Box 2, Item 4)
    - Ernst Weber President's Associate of the Polytechnic Institute of Brooklyn plaque, undated; 13938 (Box 2, Item 5)
    - Ernst Weber Defense Science Board framed citation, 1966; 13939 (Box 2, Item 6)
    - Ernst Weber Secretary of the Army's Scientific Advisory Panel framed appointment, 1961; 13940 (Box 2, Item 7)
    - Ernst Weber Secretary of the Army's Scientific Advisory Panel framed appointment, 1963; 13941 (Box 2, Item 8)
    - Ernst Weber Signal Corps research & Development Advisory Council plaque, 1959; 13942 (Box 2, Item 9)
    - Ernst Weber Department of the Army framed certificate of service, 1962; 13943 (Box 2, Item 10)
    - Howard Coonley Medal, 1966; 14063 (Box 3, Item 1)
    - Life Member or the Institute of Electrical and Electronic Engineers, undated; 14064 (Box 3, Item 2)
    - Long Island College Scientia Inopum Amica, 1967; 14065 (Box 3, Item 3)
    - Outstanding Civilian Service to the United States Army Award, undated; 14066 (Box 3, Item 4)
    - American Institute of Electrical Engineers Award for Outstanding Service as a Teacher of Electrical Engineering, 1960; 14071 (Box 3, Item 5)
    - MRI Reunion to Honor our Friend and Colleague Ernst Weber, 1969 July 2; 14121 (Bin Frame rack, Item 1)
    - Society of the Sigma Chi, 1970 May 8; 14122 (Bin Frame rack, Item 2)
    - National Academy of Sciences of the United States, diploma of election as member, 1965 April 17; 14123 (Bin Frame rack, Item 3)
    - Gold Medal of Honor for Distinguished Service in Medicine from The Long Island College Hospital, 1967 March 11; 14124 (Bin Frame rack, Item 4)
    - American institute of Electrical Engineers Fellow, 1934 June 27; 14125 (Bin Frame rack, Item 5)
    - 75th Birthday Greeting from the Transportation Planning and Engineering Program at Polytechnic Institute of Brooklyn, 1976 January 20; 14126 (Bin Frame rack, Item 6)
    - Linton E. Grinter Distinguished Service Award, 1978 October 2; 14127 (Bin Frame rack, Item 7)
    - License to Practice Professional Engineering from the University of the State of New York Education Department, 1953 January 9; 14128 (Bin Frame rack, Item 8)
    - National Academy of Engineering Founding Members Diploma, 1964 December 10; 14129 (Bin Frame rack, Item 9)
    - American Institute of Electrical Engineers Medal for Distinguished Achievement in the Teaching of Electrical Engineering, 1960 October 10; 14130 (Bin Frame rack, Item 10)
    - John E. McKeen Distinguished Alumnus clipping, 1965 March 17; 14131 (Bin Frame rack, Item 11)
    - Distinguished Service Award, Transportation Research Board/National Research Council/National Academy of Sciences, 1977 January 26; 14132 (Bin Frame rack, Item 12)
    - The American Society for Engineering Education Hall of Fame Induction, 1993; 14133 (Bin Frame rack, Item 13)
    - The Better Brooklyn Committee Citation in Recognition of Outstanding Service in the Field of Science, 1965 November 18; 14134 (Bin Frame rack, Item 14)
    - The Institute of Electrical and Electronics Engineers IEEE Education Society Achievement Award, 1990 July; 14135 (Bin Frame rack, Item 15)
    - The Institute of Electrical and Electronics Engineers Microwave Theory and Techniques Society 1977 Microwaves Career Award, 1978 June 28; 14136 (Bin Frame rack, Item 16)
    - Long Island Technology Hall of Fame award, 2005 March 9; 14813 (Bin Frame rack, Item 17)
  - Subseries C: Realia, 14062
    - National Academy of Engineering Founding Member, 1979; 14067 (Box 3, Item 6)
    - ISO Second Plenary Session, 1952; 14069 (Box 3, Item 7)
    - University of Virginia Sesquicentennial, 1969; 14070 (Box 3, Item 8)
    - ASEE Centennial, 1993; 14068 (Box 3, Item 9)
    - The Institute of Electrical and Electronics Engineers, 1971; 14074 (Box 3, Item 10)
    - Polytechnic Institute of New York Founder's Club, 1982; 14075 (Box 3, Item 11)
    - EIC pin, undated; 14082 (Box 3, Item 12)
    - Polytechnic Institute of New York President's Associate, 1854; 14076 (Box 3, Item 13)
    - ASEE pin, undated; 14077 (Box 3, Item 14)
    - ASEE Fellow pin, undated; 14078 (Box 3, Item 15)
    - Polytechnic Institute of New York President's Associate paperweight, undated; 14080 (Box 3, Item 16)
    - ISEE New York Section paperweight, 1984; 14081 (Box 3, Item 17)
    - Polytechnic Institute of Brooklyn President's Associate paperweight, undated; 14072 (Box 3, Item 18)
    - Osterreich Republik 25 Schilling coin, 1956; 14079 (Box 3, Item 19)
    - Tomorrow's Scientists and Engineers, 1972; 14083 (Box 3, Item 20)
    - Phillips slide rule, undated; 14084 (Box 4, Item 1)
    - Hemmi slide rule, undated; 14085 (Box 4, Item 2)
    - Commencement hood, undated; 14086 (Box 4, Item 3)
    - Commencement hood, undated; 14090 (Box 4, Item 4)
    - Commencement hood, undated; 14088 (Box 4, Item 5)
    - Commencement hood, undated; 14089 (Box 4, Item 6)
    - Commencement hood, undated; 14087 (Box 4, Item 7)
    - Berbecker-Osborne nickel-plated sailmaker's needles, undated; 14091 (Box 4, Item 8)
    - Rutgers University Dedication Engineering Building, 1964; 14092 (Box 4, Item 9)
    - Glass Slide Occupation Matrix, undated; 14093 (Box 4, Item 10)
    - The Institute of Electrical and Electronic Engineers 100th Anniversary, 1984; 14073 (Box 4, Item 11)
- Series II: Writings, 13246
  General
  Folder names in quotations represent a transcription of Weber's original title on the folder. Folder names without quotations represent the archivist's title for materials in the folder.
  - Subseries A: Speeches, 14094
    - Personnel in University Research, 1948; 14095 (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - New Training for Engineers, 1956; 14096 (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - New Training for Engineers, 1956; 14097 (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - Mathematical Rigor and the Relations Between Mathematics and Engineering, 1956; 14098 (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - The Age of the Electron, 1957-1958; 14099 (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - Dynamics of Engineering Education: Uniformity or Quality?, 1958; 14100 (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - Engineering Societies Building Address, 1958; 14101 (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - The Broad Spectrum, 1958; 14102 (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - What Price Leadership?, 1959; 14103 (Box 5, Folder 9)
    - The Radio Engineering of the Future, 1959; 14104 (Box 5, Folder 10)
    - How the Humanities Can Increase Literacy in Science, 1959; 14105 (Box 5, Folder 11)
    - The Broad and Beautiful Spectrum, 1959; 14106 (Box 5, Folder 12)
    - Education for Leadership, 1959; 14107 (Box 5, Folder 13)
    - Higher Education for Employed Engineers and Scientists, 1960; 14108 (Box 5, Folder 14)
    - Objectives of Science and Engineering Education, 1960; 14109 (Box 5, Folder 15)
    - Profession Society and Engineering Education, 1960; 14110 (Box 5, Folder 16)
    - Trends and Problems in Graduate Electrical Engineering Education, 1961; 14111 (Box 5, Folder 17)
    - Needed: Creative Environment, 1962; 14112 (Box 5, Folder 18)
    - Preparation for the Unexpected, 1963; 14113 (Box 5, Folder 19)
    - The Significance of Modern Engineering, 1963; 14114 (Box 5, Folder 20)
    - The Call to Leadership, 1963; 14115 (Box 5, Folder 20)
    - Opening Remarks: Symposium on Optical Masers, 1963; 14116 (Box 5, Folder 21)
    - Expanding Horizons in Engineering Education, 1964; 14117 (Box 5, Folder 22)
    - The Era of Microwaves, 1964; 14118 (Box 5, Folder 23)
    - Technological Challenges to Engineering Education, 1964; 14137 (Box 5, Folder 24)
    - Dedication of the Burndy Research Laboratory, 1964; 14138 (Box 5, Folder 25)
    - The Engineer's Responsibility to Society, 1964; 14139 (Box 5, Folder 26)
    - The Academic Climate for Civilian and Military Technology, 1964; 14140 (Box 5, Folder 27)
    - Continuing Education from the Viewpoint of the University President, 1964; 14141 (Box 5, Folder 28)
    - Science and Engineering Education on Long Island, 1965; 14142 (Box 5, Folder 29)
    - The Challenge Ahead, 1964; 14143 (Box 5, Folder 30)
    - The Challenge of Continuing Engineering Studies, 1965; 14144 (Box 5, Folder 31)
    - The Federal Government and Academic Responsibility - Partnership or Subsidy, 1965; 14145 (Box 5, Folder 32)
    - Modern Engineering Education, 1965; 14146 (Box 5, Folder 33)
    - Future Trends in Technology, 1965; 14147 (Box 5, Folder 34)
    - University, Research, and Regional Prosperity, 1965; 14148 (Box 5, Folder 35)
    - Welcome Remarks for Symposium on System Theory, 1965; 14149 (Box 5, Folder 36)
    - The Fearless and Their Trail, 1966; 14150 (Box 5, Folder 37)
    - Continuing Engineering Education, 1966; 14151 (Box 5, Folder 38)
    - The Greater Opportunities in Future Education, 1966; 14152 (Box 5, Folder 39)
    - Opening Remarks by Dr. Ernst Weber at Symposium on Modern Optics, 1967; 14153 (Box 5, Folder 40)
    - Are Society Publications Adequately Serving the Needs of their Members for State-of-the-Art Literature?, 1967; 14154 (Box 5, Folder 41)
    - Society, Not Technology, Spoils Environment, 1970; 14155 (Box 5, Folder 42)
    - AAS Symposium on Science and the Federal Government, 1970; 14156 (Box 5, Folder 43)
    - The Engineer in our Society, 1971; 14157 (Box 5, Folder 44)
    - Electrical Science in the Context of Society, 1972; 14158 (Box 5, Folder 45)
    - Technology and Culture, A Sociotechnical System, 1975; 14159 (Box 5, Folder 46)
    - The Engineer and Society, undated; 14160 (Box 5, Folder 47)
    - Sponsored Research and Academic Freedom, undated; 14161 (Box 5, Folder 48)
    - Striving for Excellence, undated; 14162 (Box 5, Folder 49)
    - Knowledge and Wisdom, undated; 14163 (Box 5, Folder 50)
    - The Current State of Physics in Engineering Education, undated; 14164 (Box 5, Folder 51)
    - The Dawn of Values, undated; 14165 (Box 5, Folder 52)
    - Communications - Link to Tomorrow, undated; 14166 (Box 5, Folder 53)
    - World Travel and Space Communication/2012 AD... A Realistic Fantasy, undated; 14167 (Box 5, Folder 54)
    - Uniform Confusion or Diverse Regimentation, undated; 14168 (Box 5, Folder 55)
    - Engineering Responsibility in Today's Governmental Research and Development Activities, undated; 14169 (Box 5, Folder 56)
    - Sixteenth International Symposium, undated; 14170 (Box 5, Folder 57)
    - Life Span of an Engineering Degree, undated; 14171 (Box 5, Folder 58)
    - Preparing Today's Engineering for Tomorrow's Challenge, undated; 14172 (Box 5, Folder 59)
    - University, Research, and Regional Prosperity, undated; 14173 (Box 5, Folder 60)
    - Manpower for Scientific Engineering, undated; 14174 (Box 5, Folder 61)
    - Freedom and Originality, undated; 14175 (Box 5, Folder 62)
    - The Space Age and IRE, undated; 14176 (Box 5, Folder 63)
    - The Shape of Things to Come, undated; 14177 (Box 5, Folder 64)
    - The Aims of Electrical Engineering Education, undated; 14178 (Box 5, Folder 65)
    - Preparing for the Unexpected, undated; 14179 (Box 5, Folder 66)
    - Be Prepared for the Unexpected, undated; 14180 (Box 5, Folder 67)
    - The Professional Groups of IRE, undated; 14181 (Box 5, Folder 68)
    - System Science - The Nondisciplinary Approach, undated; 14182 (Box 5, Folder 69)
    - Education for the Electronic Age, undated; 14183 (Box 5, Folder 70)
    - Science and Societal Engineering, undated; 14184 (Box 5, Folder 71)
    - The Challenges on the Horizon, undated; 14185 (Box 5, Folder 72)
    - The City: Teacher of Man, undated; 14186 (Box 5, Folder 73)
    - Engineering Education as a Dynamic System, undated; 14187 (Box 5, Folder 74)
    - Addresses, 1961-1969; 14188 (Box 5, Folder 75)
  - Subseries B: Papers, 14189
    - Types of Graduate Subsidy and Their Relation to Educational Values, 1953; 14190 (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - "Education for the Electronic Age", 1959; 14191 (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - A Survey of Opportunities for the Ford Foundation Support to Higher Education in Peru, 1962; 14192 (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - "Technology and Society", 1963; 14193 (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - Norelco Reporter Article, undated; 14194 (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - For Human Well-Being, undated; 14195 (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - The Case for the Rationalized M.K.S. System of Units, undated; 14196 (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - Report of the Ad Hic Committee on the Preparation of Graduate Studies Project, ASEE, undated; 14197 (Box 6, Folder 8)
    - "Graduate Study in Electrical Engineering", undated; 14198 (Box 6, Folder 9)
    - Polytechnic's Service to the Nation, undated; 14199 (Box 6, Folder 10)
    - Microwaves- Science and Art, undated; 14200 (Box 6, Folder 11)
    - Editorial for "Electronics and Communications", undated; 14201 (Box 6, Folder 12)
    - "Our Technical Society", undated; 14202 (Box 6, Folder 13)
    - Separated pages, undated; 14203 (Box 6, Folder 14)
    - "Collection of Papers Published", undated; 14204 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Subseries C: Drafts, 14205
    - World Travel and Space Communication/2012 AD... A Realistic Fantasy, undated; 14206 (Box 6, Folder 16)
    - The Broader View, undated; 14207 (Box 6, Folder 17)
    - Norelco Reporter, undated; 14208 (Box 6, Folder 18)
    - Profession - Society - And Engineering Education, undated; 14209 (Box 6, Folder 19)
    - Dynamics of Engineering Education: Uniformity or Quality, undated; 14210 (Box 6, Folder 20)
    - The Modern Technological University, undated; 14211 (Box 6, Folder 21)
    - Engineering Education in a Dynamic System, undated; 14212 (Box 6, Folder 22)
    - Historical Perspective on Engineering Education, undated; 14213 (Box 6, Folder 23)
    - Science and Societal Engineering, undated; 14214 (Box 6, Folder 24)
    - The Shape of Things to Come, undated; 14215 (Box 6, Folder 25)
    - At the Intellectual Frontier, 1963; 14216 (Box 6, Folder 26)
    - Preparation for the Unexpected, 1963; 14217 (Box 6, Folder 27)
    - The University-Industry Interface, 1966; 14218 (Box 6, Folder 28)
    - Sociotechnical Systems, 1974; 14219 (Box 6, Folder 29)
    - Opportunities and Vulnerabilities of Automation in Decision Making, 1976-1977; 14220 (Box 6, Folder 30)
  - Subseries D: Courses, 14221
    - Advanced Courses in Applied Mathematics, Engineering Deference Program at New York University, Transient Analysis of Electrical Networks, by E. Weber, 1941 June -August; 14223 (Box 6, Item 1)
    - Lectures on Ultra-short Electromagnetic Waves by Ernst Weber and W.R. MacLean (binder), 1943; 14222 (Box 6, Item 2)
    - Lectures on Ultra-short Electromagnetic Waves by Ernst Weber and W.R. MacLean (binder), 1943; 14224 (Box 6, Item 3)
    - Lectures on Ultra-short Electromagnetic Waves by Ernst Weber and W.R. MacLean (bound), 1943; 14225 (Box 6, Item 4)
    - Weber lecture materials, undated; 14226 (Box 6, Folder 31)
    - Transparencies with equations, undated; 14227 (Box 6, Folder 32)
  - Subseries E: Reprints and Published Articles, 14228
    - Weber reprints, 1928-1938, 14229 (Box 6, Folder 33)
    - Weber reprints, 1941-1947, 14230 (Box 6, Folder 34)
    - Weber reprints, 1953-1959, 14231 (Box 6, Folder 35)
    - Weber reprints, 1960-1964, 14232 (Box 6, Folder 36)
    - Weber reprints, 1965-1972, 14233 (Box 6, Folder 37)
    - Weber reprints, undated, 14234 (Box 6, Folder 38)
    - Weber MRI publications, 1956; 14237 (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - The Evolution of Electrical Engineering: A Personal Perspective monograph, 1993; 14238 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Subseries F: Publication Proofs, 14235
    - The Encyclopedia of Education chapter proof, undated; 14236 (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - Wiley publication proofs: Weber Vol. 1, undated; 14239 (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - Wiley publication proofs: Weber Vol. 1, undated; 14240 (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - Wiley publication proofs: Weber Vol. 1, undated; 14241 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Subseries G: Notes, 14242